export const questions=[
  {
    "question": "Which of these Gujarati phrases is commonly used by youngsters in Ahmedabad to express 'everything is going great' or 'all good'?",
    "options": ["Kem Cho?", "Su Chale Che?", "Jalsa!", "Kai Nathi"],
    "answer": "Jalsa!"
  },
  {
    "question": "For a stunning sunset timelapse video in Ahmedabad, which location offers the most picturesque backdrop of the city and the Sabarmati River?",
    "options": ["Law Garden Night Market", "Manek Chowk’s busy lanes", "Sabarmati Riverfront Promenade", "Inside a shopping mall"],
    "answer": "Sabarmati Riverfront Promenade"
  },
  {
    "question": "The intricate stone carving at Sidi Saiyed Mosque in Ahmedabad, often called the 'Tree of Life', is a source of awe. Which renowned Ahmedabad institution has adopted this motif as its official logo?",
    "options": ["Gujarat University", "Ahmedabad Municipal Corporation", "Indian Institute of Management Ahmedabad (IIM-A)", "Darpana Academy of Performing Arts"],
    "answer": "Indian Institute of Management Ahmedabad (IIM-A)"
  },
  {
    "question": "When an Amdavadi says they’re going for 'cutting', what are they typically referring to, especially in a relaxed social setting?",
    "options": ["Getting a haircut", "Ordering a small portion of tea", "Cutting vegetables for a snack", "Discussing a new project"],
    "answer": "Ordering a small portion of tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which specific market in Ahmedabad is famous for transforming from a bustling vegetable market in the morning to a vibrant street food hub at night, offering unique dishes like chocolate sandwiches?",
    "options": ["Teen Darwaza Market", "Law Garden Night Market", "Manek Chowk", "Ravivari Bazaar"],
    "answer": "Manek Chowk"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you're looking for hilarious relatable Gujarati comedy sketches about everyday life in Ahmedabad, which creator's channel would you most likely binge-watch for a good laugh?",
    "options": ["Hardik Tech", "Kushal Mistry", "Suhani Shah", "Tanna Dhaval"],
    "answer": "Kushal Mistry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Ahmedabad-based creator is famous for breaking down complex technological concepts and gadget reviews in easy-to-understand Gujarati, making tech accessible to everyone?",
    "options": ["Jigardhan Gadhavi", "Kajal Patel", "Tech with Hardik", "Aditi Raval"],
    "answer": "Tech with Hardik"
  },
  {
    "question": "When craving a virtual food tour of Ahmedabad, showcasing everything from the iconic Manek Chowk street food to hidden gems, which YouTube channel would be your go-to?",
    "options": ["Trending In Ahmedabad", "Suhani Shah", "Paumil Khatri", "Engineer the Gamer"],
    "answer": "Trending In Ahmedabad"
  },
  {
    "question": "An Amdavadi YouTuber is renowned for their enchanting Gujarati folk music videos and cultural content, preserving and popularizing traditional melodies for the youth. Who are they likely to be?",
    "options": ["Kinjal Dave", "Riddhi Mansuriya", "Jayesh Prajapati", "Hirva Mehta"],
    "answer": "Kinjal Dave"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Ahmedabad creator is known for their mind-bending illusions and mentalism acts, captivating audiences with their extraordinary skills and frequently appearing on YouTube to showcase their talent?",
    "options": ["Kushal Mistry", "Suhani Shah", "Tanna Dhaval", "Paumil Khatri"],
    "answer": "Suhani Shah"
  }
]

export const ChaatBotQuestion=[
   {
    "question": "How are you feeling?",
    "options": ["😄 Happy", "😌 Chill", "😫 Tired", "😎 Sassy"],
  },
  {
    "type":"Spice preference!",
    "question": "A gentle kick or a bold burst?",
    "options": ["🌶️ Mild", "🌶️🌶️ Medium", "🌶️🌶️🌶️ Hot"],
  },
    {
    "type":"Tell us your taste preference?",
    "question": "What's your chaat flavour today?",
    "options": ["🧂 Salty", "🍬 Sweet", "😋 Tangy", "🥵 Chilli"],
  },
]

export const chaatNamesByFlavour = {
  Salty: [
    "Desi Crunch Aloo Tikki Chaat",
    "Snack Mode Chan Jor Garam Chaat",
    "Salt Pop Papdi Chaat",
    "Salt Swirl Dahi Bhalla Chaat",
    "Flavour Pop Dahi Makhana Chaat",
    "Chaat House Samosa Chaat",
    "Crunch & Salt Corn Peanut Chaat",
    "Classic Gravy Ragda Tikki Chaat",
    "Savory Buzz Sev Puri Chaat",
    "Crunch Storm Mumbai Bhel Puri"
  ],
  Sweet: [
    "Meetha Crisp Papdi Chaat",
    "Drizzle-Drenched Dahi Bhalla Chaat",
    "Nutty-Witty Dahi Makhana Chaat"
  ],
  Tangy: [
    "Sassy Tang-a-licious Aloo Tikki Chaat",
    "Zingy Chan Jor Garam Chaat",
    "Crackle Pop Papdi Chaat",
    "Zesty Dip Dahi Bhalla Chaat",
    "Zingy Corn Peanut Chaat",
    "Tamarind Tilt Ragda Tikki Chaat",
    "Zest Fest Sev Puri Chaat",
    "Tingle Mix Mumbai Bhel Puri"
  ],
  Chilli: [
    "Mirchi Mash Aloo Tikki Chaat",
    "Heatwave Crunch Chan Jor Garam Chaat",
    "Teekha Twist Papdi Chaat",
    "Fiery Samosa Chaat",
    "Red-Hot Razzle Ragda Tikki Chaat",
    "Lava Pop Sev Puri Chaat",
    "Fire Trail Mumbai Bhel Puri"
  ]
};


export const creatorsByCategory = {
  "Art": [
    {
      "fullName": "Dimpy Dimpy",
      "handle": "yanaveer."
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Chauhan Pragnya",
      "handle": "artofhousewife"
    }
  ],
  "Business & Entrepreneurship": [
    {
      "fullName": "Jaidev Koushal",
      "handle": "manishloot90"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Raju Yadav Kavali",
      "handle": "businesstipstelugu"
    }
  ],
  "Cooking": [
    {
      "fullName": "Kiran Patnecha",
      "handle": "kiranbhatikitchen2905"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Meet Vaghela",
      "handle": "rupalstastytreats"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Mridula Verma",
      "handle": "meerutkadesitadka"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Savita Wankhede",
      "handle": "shagunskitchen86"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Trusha Parsaniya",
      "handle": "trushastastegujarati"
    }
  ],
  "Dance": [
    {
      "fullName": "Aayushi Vora",
      "handle": "aayushi_vora75"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Himanshu Vasava",
      "handle": "himanshuvasava"
    }
  ],
  "Education & Learning": [
    {
      "fullName": "Shailesh Zala",
      "handle": "mrtsgujarati07"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Dhairya Dholakia",
      "handle": "dhairyascreationgujarati"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Dev Soni",
      "handle": "gmhsstudyclasses"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Shailesh Makwana",
      "handle": "hngustudypoint"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Vishalaben Parmar",
      "handle": "vishalaparmar"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Bhaveshkumar Ravjibhai Variya",
      "handle": "brvariya"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Beena Thacker",
      "handle": "beenascreationgujarati427"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Girish Pidadi Plan My Study",
      "handle": "planmystudy"
    },
    {
      "fullName": "Sakshi Patel",
      "handle": "paramshantimeditation"
    }
  ]
}


export const categories = [
  'Art',
  'Automobile',
  'Business & Entrepreneurship',
  'Cooking',
  'Dance',
  'Education & Learning',
  'Entertainment',
  'Food',
  'Gaming',
  'Health',
  'Lifestyle',
  'Music',
  'News & Information',
  'Others',
  'Pets & Animals',
  'Podcast',
  'Religious',
  'Spiritual',
  'Sports',
  'Technology',
]


export const base64ToFile = (base64Data, filename) => {
  const arr = base64Data.split(',');
  const mime = arr[0].match(/:(.*?);/)[1];
  const bstr = atob(arr[1]);
  let n = bstr.length;
  const u8arr = new Uint8Array(n);

  while (n--) {
    u8arr[n] = bstr.charCodeAt(n);
  }

  return new File([u8arr], filename, { type: mime });
};


export const url="https://youtube-server1-f228ee9b9bbd.herokuapp.com"